Guide to the Nathaniel Tarn Papers, ca. 1939-2000 M1132
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2. Literary Correspondence
  - Subseries Q-5. Other Publishers' Files and Literary Materials: Miscellaneous Files
    - O'Leary, Peter (Lung) (Box 72, Folder 6)
      [Copies of email, correspondence, postcards, ts,1996-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Olson, Toby (Box 72, Folder 7)
      [Copies of email, internet articles, correspondence, postcards, ts,1997-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Palmer, Michael (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Phillips, Dennis (Littoral) (Box 72, Folder 9)
      [Copies of email, correspondence, postcard, ms notes,1998-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Sartorius, Joachim (Germany) (Box 72, Folder 10)
      [Correspondence,1999; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Ten Berge, Hans (Holland) (Box 72, Folder 11)
      [Correspondence, postcards, 1996-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Tranter, John (Australia) (Jacket) (Box 72, Folder 12)
      [Copies of email, copies of articles from the internet, ts, 1998-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Vangelisti, Paul (Ribot) (Box 72, Folder 13)
      [Material for conference of College of Neglected Science (CONS), 1997; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 72, Folder 14)
      [Mostly copies of email, copies of internet articles, some correspondence, 1997-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Weiss, Mark (Box 72, Folder 15)
      [Copies of email, some correspondence, some ts, 1999-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Wesker, Arnold (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - West, Paul (Box 72, Folder 17)
      [Photocopied diagram of small glider, inscribed, 1999; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - [Untitled folder: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1997] (Box 73, Folder 1)
      [From a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - [Untitled folder: miscellaneous correspondence, invitations, etc. 1995-1997] (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - [Untitled folder: miscellaneous correspondence, 1997-1998] (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - NT General correspondence, 2000 [1 of 2] (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - NT General correspondence, 2000 [2 of 2] (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Misc. US (Box 73, Folder 6)
      [Correspondence, copies of email, brochures, etc., 2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Misc. UK (Box 74, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, copies of email, photocopies of newspaper articles, etc., 2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Early Proses, 1960s (Box 74, Folder 2)
      [Ts of Timbre for academe with handwritten corrections, 2 other copies; carbon of material by Tarn and others; photocopied newspaper book reviews; some correspondence; some ms material; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Early Poetry Readings File, 1960s. (Box 74, Folder 3)
      [Announcements, brochures, handbills, photocopy of first newspaper book review, etc.]
    - Poetry Reading Files 1967-1971 [1 of 2] (Box 74, Folder 4)
      Correspondence connected, some 275 pages. [Announcements, brochures, handbills, photographs, etc.]
    - Poetry Reading Files 1967-1971 [2 of 2] (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Poetry Reading Files 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      Correspondence connected, circa 100 pages. [Announcements, brochures, handbills, etc.]
    - Poetry Readings, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, announcements, brochures, handbills, etc.; folder not originally listed within a group of Poetry Reading Files 1975-1996 by Tarn]
    - Poetry Readings, 1980s [1 of 2] (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Poetry Readings, 1980s [2 of 2] (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Poetry Readings, 1990s [1 of 3] (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Poetry Readings, 1990s [2 of 3] (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Poetry Readings, 1990s [3 of 3] (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - BBC Programs 1954-1969: participated in by NT usually but with many other authors. (Box 76, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, payment vouchers, carbon of ts, other material]
    - Early BBC Broadcasts, 1960s (Box 76, Folder 2)
      [Copies of radio scripts by Tarn and others, other material; folder not originally listed by Tarn]
    - BBC Scripts (Box 76, Folder 3)
      Scripts for the BBC program The Poet's Voice: 105 mimeographed scripts and interviews with Tarn, Tom Clark, George MacBeth, etc.(*)[Tarn's * indicates missing material, some of which may appear in previous folder]
    - Six poems read at Lucie-Smith's group, 11th May, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      [Ts with handwritten notes, not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Six poems read at Lucie-Smith's group, 6th October, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Page proofs of "Benares" X7, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      [Proof with handwritten notes, not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Guiness poetry prize proof (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - U.K. jobs, 1969-1970 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      [Correspondence, photocopied newspaper articles]
    - Job Offer Files: Between Princeton and Rutgers professorships, 1969-71. (Box 76, Folder 9)
      [Correspondence]
    - Job Offer and enquiries1972-76. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Job change Attempts File, 1977-81. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - National Translation Center, Austin, Texas (Box 76, Folder 12)
      Correspondence file circa 1969-70 relating to and exploration of possibly hiring NT as head of the Center.
    - Neruda Battle, 1989-1990 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      Battle with Seymour Lawrence over re-edition of NT's Selected Poems of Pablo Neruda, 1989-90.
    - Who's Who in the West, in America (Box 77, Folder 2)
      [Correspondence, ts, proofs, and other material regarding Tarn's auto-biographical sketch]
    - Literary Grants, 1980s (Box 77, Folder 3)
      [Correspondence, grant applications, mostly from the NEA, also includes New Mexico, Pennsylvania, New York, 1980s-1993; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - NEA file (Box 77, Folder 4)
      [Correspondence, applications, ts of submitted poems, other material regarding NEA grants program, mid 1970s-late 1980s]
    - Library Contents files (Box 77, Folder 5)
      [Handwritten lists, possibly mid-1980s]
    - Library moved to Santa Fe (Box 77, Folder 6)
      [Handwritten lists, n.d.; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - NT sales from library, 1970s (Box 77, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, sales vouchers, other material regarding auction of literary material by Sotheby's, London]
    - Books sold at auction-1986 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      [Correspondence, sales vouchers, catalogs,other material regarding auction of literary material by Bloomsbury Book Auctions, London]
    - Paris, 1948-51 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, etc.]
    - This Week in Paris, employment, 1948-52 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      [Photocopies of columns and articles written under the pseudonym Michel Tavriger]
    - Cheltenham Literary Festival, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Bled: International PEN Round Table, 1965. (Box 78, Folder 4)
      [Correspondence, brochures, mimeographed ts of conference papers, handwritten notes, etc.]
    - London Poetry Secretariat, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      [Correspondence, newsletters; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Bratislava Translation Conference and Societe Europeene de Culture Meetings, Prague and Moscow-Leningrad, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - U. of Colorado Writers' Conference, 1971. (Box 78, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, photocopies of newspaper articles, conference material, photographs, etc.]
    - Linguistic Institute: program guide SUNY Buffalo, July5-August27,1971 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      [Booklet; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - National Book Award Translation Panel, 1973. (Box 78, Folder 9)
      [Correspondence, memoranda, lists of nominees, etc.]
    - International Berliner Festwochen, 1964. (Box 79, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, carbon and several photocopies of Tarn's conference paper, photocopies of conference papers by others, conference material, brochures, photocopies of newspaper articles, etc.]
    - Societe Europeene de Culture, membership, 1964-68 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      [Correspondence, memoranda]
    - Cardiff Commonwealth Festival, 1965 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      [Correspondence, festival memoranda, photocopies of newspaper articles]
    - Montreal World Poetry Festival, Montreal Expo., 1967 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Knokke International Biennale, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      [Correspondence, festival memoranda, journal containing article on Tarn, photocopies of newspaper articles]
    - Havana, Cuba International Cultural Congress, 1968. (Box 79, Folder 6)
      [Correspondence, copies of ts poetry by others, photocopies of newspaper articles, etc.]
    - Associated Writing Programs Conference, Richmond Va., 1973. (Box 80, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, conference material]
    - First Cambridge, UK, Poetry Festival, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      [Correspondence, festival material]
    - First Ethnopoetics Conference, U. Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1975 [1 of 2] (Box 80, Folder 3)
      [Correspondence, conference material, hand written notes, ts and several copies of Heraldic vision]
    - First Ethnopoetics Conference, U. Wisconsin, Milwaukee, 1975 [2 of 2] (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - International Conference on Gianbattista Vico, School of Social Research, moderator, NY, 1975 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      [Correspondence, photocopies of conference papers, hand written notes, ms draft and ts of Tarn's conference paper on Robert Redfield]
    - Holland Festivals, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      [Correspondence, photocopy of Theodore Enslin essay, conference materials, etc.]
    - Dartmouth College Latin American Poetry Festival and Conference, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, photocopy of poem and essay, conference materials, etc.]
    - Second Ethnopoetics Conference: Symposium of the Whole, Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      [Conference materials]
    - Center for Contemporary Arts Conference, Santa Fe, NM, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      [Correspondence, carbon of third draft of essay Notes towards a program...of comparative aesthetics, handwritten notes, conference materials, etc.]
    - Poetry reading at Shippensburg University, October 25, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      Copies of student reviews [not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Durango Conference, 10/85 (Box 80, Folder 11)
      [Correspondence, conference materials; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Ezra Pound Conference, San Jose, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, copy of conference paper ts, conference materials]
    - Ezra Pound Conference, San Jose, 1985 [1 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 2)
      [Photcopies of articles about, and poetry by, Ezra Pound]
    - Ezra Pound Conference, San Jose, 1985 [2 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Rotterdam International Poetry Festival, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      [Correspondence, festival material, photocopies of poetry ts by others, etc.]
    - Rockefeller Center at Bellagio, Lake Como, fellowship, 1987 [1 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 5)
      [Correspondence, center informational material, photographs, etc.]
    - Rockefeller Center at Bellagio, Lake Como, fellowship, 1987 [2 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - V. Di Suervo [1 of 2] (Box 81, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, informational material, several issues of Poetry Flash, mostly regarding National Poetry Week II and III, held at Ft. Mason, San Francisco, 1988 and 1989, respectively; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - V. Di Suervo [2 of 2] (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Telluride Conference, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      [Correspondence, conference information, copied ts of Intercultural literacy and the politics of ethnopoetics; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Tucson Poetry Festival, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      [Festival material]
    - Naropa Institute, Boulder, CO., teaching, 1990s (Box 82, Folder 4)
      [Correspondence, institute informational material]
    - Berlin, Prague, Budapest readings, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      [Handout from Berlin, handpainted poster]
    - International Michel Leiris Conference, NYU., 1991 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - International Antonin Artaud Conference, U Montreal, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      [Correspondence, handwritten notes, 2 printouts of L'ethnopoetique Chez Artaud, 1 with hand written corrections, conference material]
    - International Conference on Translation Theory, Bard College, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      [Correspondence, handwritten notes, 2 draft printouts of Translation/antitraslation//culture/multiculture: some contradictions, copy of draft proposal for voice politic/body politic, copy of Sherry Simon's Translation and interlingual creation in the contact zone, conference material]
    - Temple University Creative Writing Fellowship, 1992. (Box 82, Folder 9)
      [Correspondence, handwritten notes, fellowship material]
    - Cultural Capital of Europe Conferences, Antwerpen, Belgium, 1992-93 [1 of 2] (Box 83, Folder 1)
      [Correspondence, handwritten notes, copy of Klein waar ruimte dat niet is, possibly Tarn's conference paper, conference material, brochures]
    - Cultural Capital of Europe Conferences, Antwerpen, Belgium, 1992-93 [2 of 2] (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Octavio Paz 80th Birthday Festival, New York, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      [Correspondence, handwritten notes, copy of third draft for a talk at the N.Y.C. Paz conference, conference material]
    - American-Russian poetry conferences, Stephens Institute of Technology, Hoboken, NJ, 1994-95 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Robin Blaser International Conference, Simon Fraser U, Vancouver, BC, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      [Correspondence, conference material, brochures]
    - A tribute to Octavio Paz, NY, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      [Correspondence, 2 laser copies of Paz anthropology and the future of poetry, Tarn's address at the Mexican Cultural Institute of Washington, D.C. October 1999; laser copy of talk at the Academy of American Poets Octavio Paz 80th Birthday Conference, May 14, 1994; conference material, brochures]
    - [Tarn, Nathaniel. Paz, anthropology and the future of poetry] (Box 83, Folder 7)
      [Essay printed in Trans, no. 7, 2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Kalachakra for World Peace, Bloomington, IN, 1999 [1 of 2] (Box 84, Folder 1)
      [Program booklet, Kalachakra Initiation booklet, meeting material, photocopied magazine article, brochures, maps, etc.; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Kalachakra for World Peace, Bloomington, IN, 1999 [2 of 2] (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - University of Maine conference, July 2000: Poetry of the 1960s (Box 84, Folder 3)
      [Copies of email, photcopies of poetry by others, conference material; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - Rio Grande Writers' Association [1 of 2] (Box 84, Folder 4)
      [Mostly quarterly publications and newsletters, 1977-1987]
    - Rio Grande Writers' Association [2 of 2] (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - North American Ideophonics Annual, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      [Draft publication, introduction and poetry by Tarn pp 1 and 2; not originally listed by Tarn]
    - Chax Press (Box 133, Folder 3)
      [Correspondence, mostly copies of email regarding publication of Architextures, 199-2000; from a more recent accession, no listing by Tarn]
    - [Miscellaneous poetry, essays and journal articles by others] (Box 133, Folder 4)
      [Collom, Jack. Birds of America (excerpts), copy; Fernandez, James. The interpretation of the religious symbol, copy of draft; Niccolai, Giulia. Cosmo bar; Stein come pietra miliare, laser copies; Perruchot, Claude. The liberation of writing, journal reprint; Tejada, Roberto. (Against) the self as anacoluthon, photocopy; Interview with Gary Snyder, appearing in Mountain Gazette 36 (interviewer unknown); several poems printed by Ta'Wil books and documents]
    - [Miscellaneous non-NT articles][1 of 2] (Box 133, Folder 5)
      [Tiger, Lionel; Singer, Milton; Ames, Michael M.; Krupat, Arnold; Hastings, Rafael; Benoist, Jean-Marie;Leach, Edmund; Judson, Horace Freeland; Wantanabbe, John M.; Corngold, Stanley; Jackson; Donald Dale]
    - [Miscellaneous non-NT articles][2 of 2] (Box 133, Folder 6)
      [Steiner, George; Milner, G.B.; Humphrey, Caroline; Crystal; D.; Diamond, Stanley, ed.; Harmon, William; Heller, Michael; Ackerman, Diane]
    - [Untitled folder contains photocopied ts and magazine interviews with several poets, possibly all by Lee Bartlett] (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - [Untitled folder contains correspondence, photocopied articles, essays about and by Paul De Man][1 of 2] (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - [Untitled folder contains correspondence, photocopied articles, essays about and by Paul De Man][2 of 2] (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - [Miscellaneous photocopied newspaper articles, greeting cards, correspondence, etc., 1997][1 of 2] (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - [Miscellaneous photocopied newspaper articles, greeting cards, correspondence, etc., 1997][2 of 2] (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Subscriptions (Box 134, Folder 5)
      [Binder notepad listing journal, magazine, and newspaper subscriptions]
    - Miscellaneous art, etc. [1 of 2] (Box 135, Folder 1)
      [Posters, postcards, handbills, magazine and newspaper articles, journal reprints, other miscellaneous material]
    - Miscellaneous art, etc. [2 of 2] (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - International Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences: a prospectus, 1967 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      [Brochure, Tarn mentioned as a contributor, p.27]
    - City Miner, no.10 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      [Community magazine of the San Francisco Bay Area, interview with Bob Callahan, founder[?] of Turtle Island Press, 1978]
    - Revista, Chicano-requena: vol. XI, no. 2, Summer 1983; vol. XII, no.1, Spring 1984; vol. XII, Summer, 1984 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Le Courrier du centre international d'etudes poetiques: no. 225, Janvier-Mars 2000; no. 226 Avril-Juin, 2000 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Arts and Culture in Iceland (Box 135, Folder 7)
      [Color brochure, 1990]
    - Photographs taken to Stanford, 5/21/2001 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      #1: Top left: NT at show of own paintings, French Legation, Guatemala City, 1953; top right: NT smoking, with first wife Patricia, London, circa 1957; bottom left: Rikkitikitavi villa shot with daughter Andrea, Le Zoute, Belgium, early 1960s; bottom right: NT with son Marc as baby, London, circa 1963.#2:NT in Atiteco principal's dress, Santiago Atitlan, Guatemala, 1953.#3:Left: NT, Amarapura, Burma, 1958-9; right: NT smoking at 6 Kidderpore Gardens (prior to 21 K.G.) 10.6.1960#4: NT and Pablo Neruda, London Poetry Festival, circa mid 1960s (London Express Pictures).#5: Top left: NT reading, London?, or Edinburgh? 1960s. (photo: Graham Keen); top right: NT at Francis Huxley's party, London, circa 1963 (color); bottom left: NT with Seigle, No, Giacommetti, Seigle vernissage, 12.19.67; bottom right: NT with Marcel Jacno, typographer, and Henri and No Seigle, Seigle opening.#6: Left: NT at old Jewish Cemetery, Prague, circa 1966; right: NT, profile smoking and full face, Leningrad, 1968.#7: NT at Messina Museum, Sicily, Gnostic Studies Conference, ca. 1966.#8: Left: NT, Panajachel, Guatemala, 1969. (photo: George Holton); right: NT with Jerome Rothenberg, Larry Byrd et al, Santa Fe, summer 1970.#9: NT, reading, University of Colorado, writing school, summer 1971.#10: Left: NT, New Directions used shot with Eagle Mountain patch, early 1970s (photo: David Lenfest); right: NT, Random House picture by Ellen Levine, early 1970s.#11: NT, Neruda Nobel Prize reading, YMHA, NYC, 1970s (photo: Arthur Sirdofsky).#12: NT, bearded, bird watching, Everglades, 1970s (photo: Janet Rodney).#13: Left: NT, bearded, garden, New Hope, 1975/6 (photo: Janet Rodney); right: NT, principal, Atitlan, 1979 (photo: Janet Rodney).#14: NT, as the Sun god, painted by Martin Prechtel, Santiago Atitlan, 1979 (color).#15: Top left: NT with Orientalist Lucien Biton, Seigle opening, 12/19/67; top right: NT, bearded, on NY Ferry, late 60s or early 70s; bottom left: Gaspe Region, Canada, shot with Packard cap and dachshund Yaxwan, early 80s (color); bottom right: NT, at Santiago Atitlan, May, 1979 (photo: Janet Rodney, color).#16: Left: NT with Octavio Paz, Harvard, 1970s/1980s; right: NT and Janet Rodney, New York, late 1970s?#17: Top left: NT at desk, 96 New Street, New Hope, PA, 1980s; top right: NT at door of 96 New Street, New Hope, PA, 1980s; bottom left: NT, Haiti, 1974 (photo: Lucia Woods); bottom right: NT, Haiti, 1974 (photo: Lucia Woods).#18: Left: NT, reading at Andrew Smith Gallery, Albuquerque, 1985 (photo: Chris Marquez); right: NT, [smiling] at Andrew Smith Gallery, Albuquerque, 1985 (photo: Chris Marquez).#19: Left: NT and Janet Rodney Tarn, with Ainu mat from Hokkaido trip, 1977, New Hope, PA, circa 1979?; right: NT, Gallup, NM, 8.1981 (photo: Janet Rodney).#20: NT and Janet Rodney, San Ildefonso Church, NM, early 1980s (photo: Nina Subin)#21: Left: NT, north of Summer Palace, Beijing, 1983 (photo: Janet Rodney); top right: NT, foot of Mt. Omei, 1983 (photo: Janet Rodney); bottom right: NT, Soviet Air Force Monument, Changchun, Manchuria, 1983 (photo: Janet Rodney).#22: Top left: NT, Berlin Wall just come down, taking photo; top right: NT with father and son Marc, garden of 21 Kidderpore Gardens, London, late 80s (color); bottom left: NT, Santa Fe, circa 1986 (photo: Marjana Tracy).#23: Left: NT and Janet Rodney, London, circa 1998; right: NT with mother, London, late 1990s.#24: Left: NT, Samye Monastery, Tibet, with Santa Fe sheriff star, 1990 (photo: Elizabeth Napper); right: NT, Udaipur, India, 1990 (photo: Janet Rodney).#25: NT, USS North Carolina, late 80s (photo: Janet Rodney, color).
    - Catalog of early publications [1 of 2] (Box 136, Folder 1)
      [Index card file, chronological, under Tavriger, Tarn, and Mendelson]
    - Catalog of early publications [2 of 2] (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Old membership cards (Box 137, Folder 2)
      [Membership cards for organizations, etc.]
    - [Neruda, Pablo. Four odes one song: translation by Nathaniel Tarn] (Box 146, Folder 1)
      [Page proofs, art work by Richard Bigus, for Labyrinth Editions, 1990]
    - [Art from sketch book for front cover of At the western gates, other material] (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - [Photographs and correspondence from Adelia Parker-Castro, 1980s] (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Subseries Q-6. Other Publishers' Files and Literary Materials: Posters and Oversized Artwork
    - The Language Animal: George Steiner lecture announcement [color poster, 3/26/69, 44cm x 34cm] (Box 1000, Folder 17)
    - No It: John Latham/Trigram Press publishing announcement [color poster, 1967, 75cm x 51cm] (Box 1000, Folder 18)
    - International Times, the Invisible Generation #5.5 publishing announcement [Color poster, 1966, 75cm x 58cm] (Box 1000, Folder 19)
    - International Times publishing announcement [2 copies, color poster, n.d., 75cm x 58cm] (Box 1000, Folder 20)
    - Miracle Mouth [2 copies, color poster, n.d., 75cm x 58cm] (Box 1000, Folder 21)
    - Afterthought [ color poster, Bob Masse, 1/6/67, 50cm x 36cm] (Box 1000, Folder 22)
    - The Doors (and others)[color concert poster, Bob Masse, 7/20?/67, 51cm x 35cm] (Box 1000, Folder 23)
    - The Yardbirds (and others) [color concert poster, Bob Masse, 7/31/67, 56cm x 37cm] (Box 1000, Folder 24)
    - The Jefferson Airplane/ Trips Festival [color concert poster, Bob Masse, May 27/?, 51cm x 35cm] (Box 1000, Folder 25)
    - The Grateful Dead (and others) [color concert poster, Bob Masse, circa 7/13/67, 54cm x 35cm] (Box 1000, Folder 26)
    - Deacons [color poster, Bob Masse, 1967, 57cm x 34cm] (Box 1000, Folder 27)
    - Nu-Dimensions [color poster, Bob Masse, 1967, 56cm x 35cm] (Box 1000, Folder 28)